(Sheldon:)Fine. In the interest
of preserving our friendship...
- We're not friends.
- Well...
(Sheldon:)...that's a little hard to hear,
but all right.
(Sheldon:)As you know, the essence of diplomacy
is compromise.
(Sheldon:)With that in mind,
l propose the following.
l will take Rothman's office...
(Sheldon:)...and you will find a way
to be okay with that.
How about I take Rothman's office
and you go suck a lemon?
(Sheldon:)You sure I can't get you
that cup of tea?
(Raj:)How about you decide this with
Rock, Paper, Scissors, Lizard, Spock?
What the frig is that?
Rock, Paper, Scissors, Lizard, Spock...
...was created by lnternet pioneer
Sam Kass...
(Sheldon:)...as an improvement
on the game Rock, Paper, Scissors.
(Sheldon:)All hail Sam Kass.
(Sheldon:)Hail.